(Penny:)So, Amy, I've
been wondering,
(Penny:)are you and Sheldon going
to be sharing a room?
(Amy:)No, we discussed it.
(Amy:)We decided we didn't want
to jeopardize our relationship
(Amy:)by getting to know
each other too well.
(Sheldon:)Indeed. Nothing sours
a friendship more
(Sheldon:)than over-familiarity
with someone's toilet routine.
(Leonard:)I can vouch for that.
(Penny:)Hey.
Not you, him.
(Penny:)Oh. Thanks.
(Leonard:)Although yours
was an eye-opener.
(Amy:)Don't worry, Penny.
(Amy:)You're my plus-one.
You'll bunk with me.
(Amy:)And FYI, travel
makes me constipated,
(Amy:)so I'm the ideal
hotel roommate.
(Penny:)Terrific.
(Penny:)Are we there yet?
(Bernadette:)I hope we get there in time
to see the keynote address.
(Howard:)Really? You want to see
the keynote?
Yeah, it sounds fun.
"Super bacteria:
global apocalypse or
exciting research opportunity?"
(Howard:)Actually, I was thinking we
could go straight to the room